Guide to the University Archives Poster Collection, 1935-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List
  - The Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Marigolds, 1972 November 9 (Box 4)
  - Sierra Leone Dance Troupe, 1971 October 14 (Box 4)
  - Siberian Dancers and Singers of Omsk, 1971 February 17 (Box 4)
  - The Nutcracker, 1971 December 14 (Box 4)
  - Harkness Ballet, 1972 October 17 (Box 4)
  - The National Ballet, 1972 February 9 (Box 4)
  - Carl Otto Bartning Exhibition, 1972 September-November 5 (Box 4)
  - Burlington Choir Boys, (no year) April 15 (Box 4)
  - Museum Without Walls Film Series, 1972 September 17, 24, October 1, 8, 15 (Box 4)
  - Dance Black Presents "Myriad in Motion," 1978 February 10 (Box 4)
  - Dance Black, 1972 November 30 (Box 4)
  - Jose Limon Dance Company, 1966 February 24 (Box 4)
  - The Student Union presents Peru, Saga of the Inca Empire (March 1), Peter Selz on "Directions in Kinetic Sculpture" (March 2), and Reynold Price reading from A Generous Man (March 3), no year (Box 4)
  - Undergraduate Student Book Collection Contest, 1968 April 15 (Box 4)
  - Arthur Ferguson on "Book Bindings," 1949 November 14 (Box 4)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre, (no year) December 8 (Box 4)
  - Adaptation-Next, (no year) December 8 (Box 4)
  - Curlew River, 1968 October 25 (Box 4)
  - The Parvarim, (no year) April 8 (Box 4)
  - The River Niger, (no year) March 23 (Box 4)
  - Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass, (no year) March 4 (Box 4)
  - The Prisoner of Second Avenue, (no year) January 17 (Box 4)
  - Alexis Weissenberg, (no year) February 20 (Box 4)
  - Itzhak Perlman, 1983 October 5 (Box 4)
  - L'Orchestre National Francais, 1970 October 27 (Box 4)
  - Marcel Marceau, (no year) October 28 (Box 4)
  - Two Gentlemen of Verona, (no year) October 17 (Box 4)
  - The Duke University Wind Symphony presents "A Viennese Ball," (no year) October 8 (Box 4)
  - Your Arms Too Short to Box with God, (no year) February 26 (Box 4)
  - Jean-Bernard Pommier, (no year) November 7 (Box 4)
  - Applause, (no year) January 21 (Box 4)
  - Baroque Concert, (no year) September 24 (Box 4)
  - Joe College, 1971 April 22-24 (Box 4)
  - Duke University Music Conference "Improvisation," (no year) February 19 (Box 4)
  - Durham Civic Choral Society, (no year) March 23 (Box 4)
  - American Dance Festival Advertisement (Box 4)
  - Duke Dance presents "Theatre Theatre Movie Movie," (no year) November 31-December 1 (Box 4)
  - Performing Arts Committee Schedule, (no year) (Box 4)
  - Anyone Can Whistle (Hoof 'N' Horn), (no year) June 5-6 (Box 4)
  - Minor White Art Exhibition, (no year) November 23-December 18 (Box 4)
  - Quartetto Beethoven di Roma, (no year) November 15 (Box 4)
  - American String Quartet, (no year) February 7 (Box 4)
  - Dorian Wind Quintet, (no year) April 11 (Box 4)
  - The Rogeri Trio, (no year) March 21 (Box 4)
  - North Carolina Symphony, (no year) December 3 (Box 4)
  - Claude Frank Master Class and Recital, (no year) March 16-19 (Box 4)
  - North Carolina Symphony, (no year) November 22 (Box 4)
  - The Atlanta Ballet, (no year) April 10-11 (Box 4)
  - One Act Plays, (no year) May 11-12 (Box 4)
  - Journey Into Blackness, (no year) April 9 (Box 4)
  - A Concert of Chamber Music, (no year) November 11 (Box 4)
  - Chicago, (no year) October 24 (Box 4)
  - Utopia Limited (Durham Savoyards), 1981 April 24-25 (Box 4)
  - The Parvarim Program (Box 4)
  - Grease, undated (Box 4)
  - A Symposium on Kidney Transplantation, (no year) April 25 (Box 4)
  - Dr. Michael E. DeBakey on "Research in Heart Disease," (no year) March 21 (Box 4)
  - Demonstration Notice, 1975 February 28 (Box 4)
  - Little Mary Sunshine (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1970 December 10, 12-14 (Box 4)
  - Jim Belushi, (no year) March 25 (Box 4)
  - Music in the Museum, (no year) February 19, March 25, April 29 (Box 4)
  - Bethia Brehmer Natural and Symbolic Color Etchings, (no year) August 29-October 4 (Box 4)
  - Today's Woman Series, (no year) April-May (Box 4)
  - International Year of the Child Festival, (no year) November 3 (Box 4)
  - The Apple Tree (Hoof 'N' Horn), (no year) October 28-30, November 4-6, 11, 13 (Box 4)
  - North Carolina Symphony, (no year) May 11 (Box 4)
  - The Apple Tree (The Divinity Players), (no year) April 12-14 (Box 4)
  - Duke Dance Program Annual Faculty-Student Concert, (no year) December 7-8 (Box 4)
  - I'm Getting My Act Together and Taking It On the Road, undated (Box 4)
  - Mike Cross, (no year) October 10 (Box 4)
  - Randy Levin, (no year) April 5 (Box 4)
  - Freewater Friday Film Series, 1974 January-April (Box 4)
  - Freewater Thursday Film Series, 1974 January-April (Box 4)
  - American's Caste System: Sexism and Racism in our Society, (no year) April 8-11 (Box 4)
  - Edgar Brooks on "Power, Law, Right and Love: A Study in Political Values," (no year) February 6-8 (Box 4)
  - Dr. Kenneth W. Thompson on "Christian Ethics and the Dilemmas of Foreign Policy," (no year) March 22-24 (Box 4)
  - John Wild on "Christianity and Politics," (no year) November 18-19, 21 (Box 4)
  - Dr. Carl J. Friedrich on "Transcendent Justice: The Religious Dimension of Constitutionalism," (no year) April 3-5 (Box 4)
  - Jonathan Crewe on "Shakespeare's Figure of Lucrece: Gendered Reading and Political Interest," (no year) December 1 (Box 4)
  - Catherine Ingraham on "The Faults of Architecture: Territory, Partition, King Lear," (no year) November 4 (Box 4)
  - A Panel Discussion on "Hindus, Muslims, Sikhs in India: Challenge to a Secular State," (no year) April 13 (Box 4)
  - Carol Wincenc, (no year) December 11 (Box 4)
  - Katherine Shelburne Exhibit "Primitives: Fanciful, Gothic, and Alaskan," (no year) January 27-February 22 (Box 4)
  - B Stewart McDonald Exhibit "The Enchantment of Light," (no year) September 26-October 21 (Box 4)
  - "Student Printmakers: A First Edition," (no year) October 1-31 (Box 4)
  - Photographs by Chuck Lewis, (no year) January 29-February 23 (Box 4)
  - Wilson Bryan Key on "Subliminal Seduction," undated (Box 4)
  - Margot Richter Exhibit, (no year) August 26-September 30 (Box 4)
  - Jimmy W. Crawford Photographs, (no year) October 2-29 (Box 4)
  - Mephisto (film), undated (Box 4)
  - Oxymora, (no year) March 1 (Box 4)
  - Duke Students for Energy Conservation, undated (Box 4)
  - Bob Rankin presents "Mr. Carrot Visits Duke," (no year) October 24-November 18 (Box 4)
  - Tom Jackson on "Guerilla Tactics in the Job Market: How to Get the Job You Want," (no year) November 28 (Box 4)
  - Bonnie Raitt in Concert, undated (Box 4)
  - Elaine Harbison Exhibit, (no year) January 12-February 7 (Box 4)
  - Herbert McClure Exhibit, (no year) August 24-September 24 (Box 4)
  - Mike Cross, (no year) October 8 (Box 4)
  - Stoppard's Hamlet and The Actor's Nightmare (The Duke Repertory Theater Company), (no year) March 29 (Box 4)
  - Duke University Chorale, (no year) September 26 (Box 4)
  - Sylvia Heyden Tapestries, (no year) November 19-December 19 (Box 4)
  - Todd Cull Exhibit, (no year) November 19-December 19 (Box 4)
  - Royal Winnipeg Ballet, (no year) March 15 (Box 4)
  - Jazz on the Green, (no year) September 12 (Box 4)
  - "Moving Cultures: Latin America at Duke" Exhibit, (no year) January 8-February 25 (Box 4)
  - City of Angels, (no year) April 15-18, 22-25, May 14-15 (Box 4)
  - The Arts in Times of War, (no year) February 10 (Box 4)
  - Assassins (Hoof 'N' Horn), (no year) January 21-24, 28-31 (Box 4)
  - Pippin (Hoof 'N' Horn), (no year) October 16-19, 23-26 (Box 4)
  - Dave Brubeck Quartet, undated (Box 4)
  - Celebrating 100 Years with the Durham Sun, undated (Box 4)
  - A Garden Concert (Duke University Wind Symphony), (no year) October 2 (Box 4)
  - Tennessee Children's Dance Ensemble, (no year) June 25-26 (Box 4)
  - Duke University Dance Program, (no year) April 10-11 (Box 4)
  - Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, (no year) April 15 (Box 4)
  - Uto Ughi, undated (Box 4)
  - All of Me Free Screening, (no year) April 23 (Box 4)
  - Julian Bond, (no year) April 1 (Box 4)
  - Julliard String Quartet, (no year) March 3 (Box 4)
  - Fresk Quartet, (no year) February 11 (Box 4)
  - The Red Clay Ramblers and Shady Grove, (no year) September 14 (Box 4)
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, undated (Box 4)
  - Umbria at Duke Jazz Festival, (no year) November 2-4 (Box 4)
  - The North Carolina Symphony, (no year) November 21 (Box 4)
  - box 5 (Box 5)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1980 April (Box 5)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1979 November (Box 5)
  - Three Concerts In Memoriam of Julia Mueller, 1978 April 1, 10, and 23 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Duke Collegium Musicum, 1974 April 23 (Box 5)
  - David Barison, 1973(?) October 31 (Box 5)
  - An Evening of New Music, 1977(?) April 12 (Box 5)
  - The Duke University Wind Symphony, 1976 September 26 (Box 5)
  - Lisa Crawford in Harpsichord Recitals and Master Class, 1976 October 24-25 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Robert Elwood Senior Recital, 1977(?) January 29 (Box 5)
  - Jean-Pierre Rampal, 1980 January 15 (3 copies) (Box 5)
  - Bach Aria Group, 1978 November 17 (Box 5)
  - The London Symphony Orchestra, 1976 March 23 (Box 5)
  - Leontyne Price, 1974 January 25 (Box 5)
  - Joni, 1974(?) March 24 (Box 5)
  - Holly Near, (no year) November 14 (Box 5)
  - Vienna Chamber Orchestra, 1980 January 29 (Box 5)
  - The North Carolina Chamber Players Fall Festival of Music, 1980 November 16-18 (Box 5)
  - North Carolina Symphony Gala, 1980 January 8 (Box 5)
  - Ruth Laredo, 1980 September 6 (Box 5)
  - Viennese Gala with The Tonkuenstler Orchestra of Vienna, 1980 October 14 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Liona Boyd, 1980 November 20 (Box 5)
  - Francis Perry, 1980 May 21 (3 copies) (Box 5)
  - Bella Davidovich, 1980 September 18 (Box 5)
  - Philippe Entremont, Vienna Chamber Orchestra, 1980 January 29 (Box 5)
  - Recitals in the Chapel, 1980 May 20 (Box 5)
  - The North Carolina Chamber Players Recital Series, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Salvatore Accardo, 1980 March 19 (Box 5)
  - North Carolina Symphony, 1980 February 11 (Box 5)
  - The Duke University Opera Festival, 1980 May 31-June 14 (Box 5)
  - Colloquium on French Organ Music, 1980(?) April 12-13 (Box 5)
  - The Durham Civic Choral Society and The North Carolina Chamber Players, 1979 October 28 (Box 5)
  - Mozart's Baroque Style, 1979 November 28 (Box 5)
  - The Durham Civic Choral Society, 1979 May 13 (Box 5)
  - Budapest Symphony Orchestra, 1979 January 17 (Box 5)
  - Duke Psychiatry Songwriters' Festival Benefit Show, 1978 May 19 (Box 5)
  - La Boheme, 1978 March 13 (3 copies) (Box 5)
  - The Duke University Wind Symphony Presents A Viennese Ball, 1978(?) February 25 (Box 5)
  - The Romeros, 1978 February 3 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Pepe Romero, 1978(?) October 31 (Box 5)
  - Atlanta Symphony Orchestra, 1977 October 4 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Four Operas in Four Weeks, 1977 June 25, July 2, 9, and 16 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - The Duke University Chorale Fall Concert, 1977 November 13 (Box 5)
  - Vienna Choir Boys, 1976 January 27 (Box 5)
  - Andres Segovia, 1976 February 24 (Box 5)
  - The National Opera Company Presents The Magic Flute, 1976 January 30 (Box 5)
  - Dizzy Gillespie, The Mitchell-Ruff Duo and The Duke Jazz Ensemble, 1976 February 19 (Box 5)
  - Lazar Berman, 1976 October 7 (Box 5)
  - Strasbourg Philharmonic Orchestra, 1975(?) March 6 (Box 5)
  - Duke University 50th Anniversary Weekend Musical Events, 1975 April 11-13 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - The National Opera Company Presents The Elixir of Love, 1974 March 6 (Box 5)
  - Julian Bream, 1974(?) October 3 (Box 5)
  - The Houston Symphony, 1973(?) March 14 (Box 5)
  - Piedmont Chamber Orchestra, 1973 April 18 (Box 5)
  - Alexis Weissenberg, 1973(?) February 20 (Box 5)
  - Benny Goodman, 1973(?) October 13 (Box 5)
  - Durham Civic Choral Society, 1973 December 16 (Box 5)
  - The Duke University Chorale in Concert, 1973 March 29 (Box 5)
  - Zara Nelsova, 1973 December 3 (Box 5)
  - The Duke University Chorale, 1973 October 19 (Box 5)
  - National Chinese Opera Theatre, 1974(?) October 31-November 1 (Box 5)
  - Tosca (The Goldovsky Grand Opera Theater), 1973 November 9 (Box 5)
  - Benny Goodman, (no year) October 13 (Box 5)
  - The Turtles and the New York Rock and Roll Ensemble, (no year) September 28 (Box 5)
  - The Preservation Hall Jazz Band, 1977 February 4 (Box 5)
  - "An Organ Tour of Europe" by Charles Krigbaum, 1977 March 27 (Box 5)
  - The Duke University Chorale in Concert, 1977 March 19 (Box 5)
  - Lazar Berman, 1976 February 12 (Box 5)
  - The Preservation Jazz Co. in "The Resolve and the Return," 1976 July 14 (Box 5)
  - Melos Quartet, (no year) October 9 (Box 5)
  - Loren Withers, 1977 January 21 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1976 October 15 (Box 5)
  - Barbara Lister-Sink, 1976 October 3 (Box 5)
  - "American Sampler: American Music From the Turn of the Century," 1976 October 1 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - La Traviata(Canadian Opera), 1977 February 18 (Box 5)
  - Alicia de Larrocha, 1976 December 2 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Leningrad Symphony Orchestra, 1977 February 23 (Box 5)
  - Tokyo String Quartet, 1977(?) March 12 (Box 5)
  - Mike Cross, (no year) February 7 (Box 5)
  - Blackstone Magic Show, 1978 December 3 (Box 5)
  - Grease, 1974 February 15 (Box 5)
  - Fiddler on the Roof (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1980(?) April 4-5 and May 9-10 (Box 5)
  - Shut Up. We're Singing (Hoof 'N' Horn), (no year) January 26-28 and February 3, 7, 10 (Box 5)
  - Les Grands Ballets Canadiens, 1980 February 2 (Box 5)
  - Julius Caesar (The National Shakespeare Company), 1980 January 18 (Box 5)
  - P.S. Your Cat Is Dead, 1980 February 8 (Box 5)
  - Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre, 1980 February 19 and 20 (Box 5)
  - Ballet Theater Company of Raleigh, 1980 March 22 and 23 (Box 5)
  - The Lion in Winter, 1980 December 8 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1980-1981 (Box 5)
  - Gertrude Stein, 1980 November 14 (Box 5)
  - Vespers, 1981 February 15 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Pauline Koner Dance Consort, 1980 March 28 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Be Jubilant My Feet, 1980 May 19 (Box 5)
  - The Gin Game, 1980 September 25 (Box 5)
  - North Carolina Dance Theater, 1980 December 2 (Box 5)
  - Summer Theater at Duke, 1980 (Box 5)
  - The Triangle Dance Guild, 1979-1980 Season (Box 5)
  - Ain't Misbehavin', 1980 March 23 (Box 5)
  - Summer Theatre at Duke, 1979 (Box 5)
  - Julie Harris in The Belle of Amherst, 1979 November 16 (Box 5)
  - Ohio Ballet, 1979 March 22-23 (Box 5)
  - Estelle Parsons in Miss Margarida's Way, 1979 October 4 (Box 5)
  - Leonard Bernstein's Mass, 1978 March 26-29 (Box 5)
  - Neil Simon's California Suite, 1978 November 11 (Box 5)
  - Windom Plays "Thurber," 1978 September 22 (Box 5)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre, 1978 October 20 (Box 5)
  - Bubbling Brown Sugar, (no year) March 19 (Box 5)
  - Kathryn Posen Dance Company, 1977 November 10 (Box 5)
  - Another Saturday Night (Hoof 'N' Horn), (no year) December 2, 3, 4, and 10 (Box 5)
  - Duke Dance Lapis Lazuli, (no year) April 7 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Oh Coward!, 1975 March 4 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Cincinnati Ballet Company, 1975(?) February 27-28 (Box 5)
  - Chamber Dance Group, 1974 March 1 (Box 5)
  - Harkness Ballet, 1974(?) March 7 (Box 5)
  - The Sunshine Boys, 1974 November 17 (Box 5)
  - Broadway at Duke Schedule, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Lado: The Yugoslav National Dance and Folk Ensemble, 1973 January 28 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Applause, 1973(?) January 21 (Box 5)
  - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1973(?) April 13-14, May 11-12 (Box 5)
  - Summer Theater at Duke Open Auditions, 1973 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire (Duke Players), 1973(?) November 30, December 1-2, 6-9 (Box 5)
  - The Intimate P.D.Q. Bach, 1973 March 2 (Box 5)
  - The Nutcracker, 1973 December 12 (Box 5)
  - Feiffer's People, 1973(?) June 8-10 (Box 5)
  - Saint Joan (The National Shakespeare Company), 1973 November 30 (Box 5)
  - Sticks and Bones (Summer Theater at Duke), 1973(?) July 13-15 (Box 5)
  - A Thousand Clowns (Summer Theater at Duke), 1973(?) June 29-30, July 1 (Box 5)
  - Spoon River Anthology (Summer Theater at Duke), 1973(?) June 22-24 (Box 5)
  - Bayanihan (Philippine Dance Company), 1973(?) October 21 (Box 5)
  - Sleuth, 1973(?) March 5 (Box 5)
  - Summer Dance (undated) (Box 5)
  - Ballet Nacional Festivales de Espana, 1976 November 21 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - My Fair Lady (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1977(?) April 2-3 and May 7-8 (Box 5)
  - Rod Rodgers Dance Company, (no year) March 17 (Box 5)
  - Summer Theater at Duke (no year), U.S.A. (May 21-23) and Twelfth Night (May 28-30) (Box 5)
  - Summer Theater at Duke (no year), The Devil's Disciple (June 25-27, July 2-4) and Beyond the Fringe (June 26-27) (Box 5)
  - Summer Theater at Duke 1976, Dylan (June 11-13, 19-20) and Beyond the Fringe (June 17-18, 26-27) (Box 5)
  - The Roar of the Greasepaint, The Smell of the Crowd (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1976(?) December 3-5 (Box 5)
  - Gypsy (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1976 October 22-24, 29-31 and November 5-7 (Box 5)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre, 1976 October 13 (Box 5)
  - The Tempest (The New Shakespeare Company, San Francisco), 1977(?) April 8 (Box 5)
  - Synergy (Synergic Foundation for the Arts), 1977(?) February 11-12, 18-19 (Box 5)
  - Don't Bother Me, I Can't Cope, 1976 October 8 (Box 5)
  - The Birmingham Ballet on Tour, 1976(?) (Box 5)
  - Dances We Dance—Betty Jones and Fritz Ludin, (no year) September 24 (Box 5)
  - The Taming of the Shrew, 1976 December 9 (Box 5)
  - Rod Rodgers Dance Company, 1977(?) March 17 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous Publicity Notices (Box 5)
  - Joe College Week, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Street Arts Celebration, 1980 September 13 (Box 5)
  - Indian Heritage Week, 1980(?) September 20-26 (Box 5)
  - Heavyweight Championship Fights, 1947-1974 (Box 5)
  - Duke University Union Information Poster (Box 5)
  - Duke University Artists Series 1979-1980 (Box 5)
  - ArtsFare (Summer Festival of Arts), 1980 (Box 5)
  - The Archive Publicity Poster, 1980 (Box 5)
  - ArtsFare (Summer Festival of Arts), North Carolina Chamber Players, 1979 (Box 5)
  - ArtsFare (Summer Festival of Arts), 1979 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Octoberfest, 1979 October 12 (Box 5)
  - Blackburn Literary Festival, 1978 March 26-April 2 (Box 5)
  - Duke University Artists Series, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Duke University Union Performing Arts Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Duke Artists Series, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Duke Artists Series, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Duke University 50th Anniversary Weekend Events Calendar (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - USA-USSR Summer Arts Festival, 1974 July 3-7 (Box 5)
  - Allied Arts of Durham, Inc. Spring Classes, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Allied Arts of Durham, Inc. Summer Classes, 1973 (Box 5)
  - SpringFest, 1973 May 19-20 (Box 5)
  - The Performing Arts Committee of the Duke University Union Schedule, 1973-1974(?) (Box 5)
  - A Track and Field Spectacular: 30 Performers from the 1972 Olympic Games, 1973 May 12 (Box 5)
  - The New Communicators (on NBC), (no year) May 23 (Box 5)
  - Duke University Union Performing Arts Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
  - Duke Union Committee on the Performing Arts, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Phi Kappa Psi Celebrity Auction, 1976 October 1 (Box 5)
  - International Day, 1977(?) April 2 (Box 5)
  - Junior League Tennis Classic with John Newcombe and Bill Scanlon, 1977 April 18 (Box 5)
  - Christmas Tree Sale, (no year) December 5-21 (Box 5)
  - ASDU Book Fair, 1976(?) January 8-January 14 (Box 5)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 1980 Spring (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Freewater Films, 1980 Spring (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Freewater Films, 1980 Fall (Box 5)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 1980 Fall (Box 5)
  - Freewater Film Society, 1979 Fall (Box 5)
  - Freewater Films, 1979 Summer (Box 5)
  - Freewater Films, 1979 Spring (Box 5)
  - Freewater Films, 1975 Spring (Box 5)
  - Freewater Films, 1974 Fall (Box 5)
  - Charles Chaplin in Monsieur Verdoux (film), 1974(?) April 20 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Charles Chaplin in The Great Dictator (film), 1974(?) March 30-31 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - The Chaplin Revue: A Selection of Three Previously Unavailable Shorts, (no year) March 2 (Box 5)
  - Charlie Chaplin in The Kid, (undated) (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Charlie Chaplin in The Gold Rush, (undated) (Box 5)
  - Charlie Chaplin in The Circus, (undated) (Box 5)
  - Charlie Chaplin in City Lights, (undated) (Box 5)
  - Charlie Chaplin in Limelight, (undated) (Box 5)
  - Charlie Chaplin's A King in New York, (undated) (Box 5)
  - The Misfits, (no year) October 5 (Box 5)
  - Red River, (no year) November 15 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous Movie Schedule, (undated) (Box 5)
  - Rules of the Game, (no year) October 11 (Box 5)
  - Day of Wrath, (no year) October 25 (Box 5)
  - Greed, (no year) September 20 (Box 5)
  - Blow-Up, (no year) October 12 (Box 5)
  - Freewater Films, 1976 Fall (Box 5)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 1976 Spring (Box 5)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 1977 Spring (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - Quadrangle Pictures Presents A Midsummer Night's Dream (The New York City Ballet), 1976(?) (Box 5)
  - Meredith Johnson, 1980 October 27-November 21 (Box 5)
  - The Art of Work, 1979 December 1-1980 January 11 (Box 5)
  - Victor Vasarely Exhibition, 1980 August 9-September 21 (Box 5)
  - Eddie Smith Recent Works, 1979 July 11-August 31 (Box 5)
  - Art Auction (sponsored by Phi Kappa Sigma Fraternity), 1978 February 26 (Box 5)
  - Rod Farb Photography Exhibition, 1978 June 3-9 (Box 5)
  - Photo Silk Screens, 1975 March 17-April 16 (Box 5)
  - Exhibition and Sale of Original Graphic Art, 1975 January 30 (Box 5)
  - Perspektywa Polska: An Exhibition of the History of Polish Culture, 1975 February 23-March 23 (Box 5)
  - Hide Oshiro Prints and Drawings, 1976(?) November 15-December 18 (Box 5)
  - Social Problems—The Vision of Photography (student photographs), 1977 March 14-21 (Box 5)
  - Mark Lane on "Who Killed Kennedy," 1975 November 13 (Box 5)
  - Frederic Storaska on "How To Say No To A Rapist—And Survive," 1980(?) October 9 (Box 5)
  - Frederic Storaska on "How To Say Not To A Rapist—And Survive," 1976(?) October 20 (this is a different occasion from the 1980 October 9 lecture) (Box 5)
  - Michael Novak on "The War of Ideas: The Theology of Democratic Capitalism," 1980 February 4 (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - George Plimpton on "The Paper Lion," 1979 November 6 (Box 5)
  - Elizabeth McAlister on "The Cost of Peacemaking in the Nuclear Age," 1976 April 2 (Box 5)
  - Neil Newhouse, ASDU President, 1973(?) (Box 5)
  - Marcia Gillespie, Editor of Essence, on "Media as Propaganda," 1977 February 22 (Box 5)
  - Ralph Nader on "Corporate Responsibility and Consumer Protection," 1976 September 29 (Box 5)
  - Hugh Sidey on "The Race for the Presidency," 1976 September 15 (Box 5)
  - Jack Anderson on "The News Behind the Headlines," 1976 November 17 (Box 5)
  - box 6 (Box 6)
  - Institutional Equity, Call and Response: Listening, Learning and Living the Legacy, January 2006, A2007-2 (Box 6)
  - NC Festival of the Book, 2006 April 24-30 (Box 6)
  - Duke University Improv, 2004 April 15 (Box 6)
  - Duke University Improv, 2005 April 28 (Box 6)
  - Cable 13 Schedule, 2004 Spring (Box 6)
  - All of the Above (A compilation of monologues written and performed by Duke women), (no year) April 29-30, May 1 (Box 6)
  - Cross Currents: Conversations about Collecting and Documenting African and African American Life, 2005 November 18 (Box 6)
  - Go Devils! From The News and Observer, undated (Box 6)
  - Freewater Films, 1989 Spring (Box 6)
  - Loren Withers, 1971 November 12 (Box 6)
  - Quad Flicks, 1971 Summer (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Duke Collegium Musicum presents "A Petrarch Concert," (no year) October 29 (Box 6)
  - Duke Collegium Musicum presents "Music During the Schism: French Sacred and Secular Music During the Late XIVth Century," (no year) December 10 (Box 6)